ticketbis.net 2013-08-06

# PRIVACY

### **TERMS AND CONDITIONS - PRIVACY AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION ON WWW.TICKETBIS.NET**

Acceptance of the present conditions implies comformity and express consent to the treatment of the information facilitated to TODOENTRADAS, S.L. through the Website [www.ticketbis.net](http://www.ticketbis.net/). 

**1\. Personal Information.**

Through the registration procedure on [www.ticketbis.net](http://www.ticketbis.net/) the User provides TODOENTRADAS, S.L. the following personal information (hereinafter, the "personal information"). 

  * First name and Surname;
  * E-mail address and contact telephone number;
  * Credit or debit card number or bank account information depending on the Users choice.

**2\. Automated Treatment**

In accordance with Organic Law 15/1999 on the Protection of Personal Information of Spain and its regulations, in compliance with articles 5 and 6, the entity responsible for the website informs all website Users who provide or will provide personal information that it will be incorporated in an automated catalogue. 

**3\. Purpose.**

The purpose of collection and automated treatment of Personal Information is solely for the maintenance of the relationship established in the General and Particular Terms and Conditions of Use, in the management, administration, provision, expantion, and improvement of Services, and in the adaptation of the Service to the taste and preferences of the Users, in the design of new related services, in the delivery of Service updates, in the delivery of publicity related to the Services and other products and services offered by TODOENTRADAS, S.L. or through TODOENTRADAS, S.L. currently and in the future, in the fullfilment of direct marketing of said products and services. The purpose of the automated treatment of Personal Information includes the sending of polling questionaires that the User is not obligated to answer. 

**4\. Communications.**

With acceptance of of our policy for privacy and data protection, the User accepts that TODOENTRADAS, S.L. may communicate the Personal Information to the rest of the companies belonging to the Corporate Group regardless of their domicile, with the same purposes that have been indicated in the preceeding paragraph. In any case, TODOENTRADAS, S.L. guarantees the maintenance of confidentiality and secure treatment of Personal Information in these international movements. The use of Personal Information of the foreign companies belonging to the TODOENTRADAS, S.L. corporate group will be confined to the contents of this document. 

**5\. Security Measures**.

TODOENTRADAS, S.L. guarantees that it has taken the oportune and necessary security measures in its instalations, systems, catalogues, as well as the confidential treatment of Personal Information in accordance with the applicable Legislation in effect. 

TODOENTRADAS, S.L. also guarantees the mantenance of confidentiality of Personal Information and safe treatment thereof in international movements. However, TODOENTRADAS, S.L. shall reveal to the competent public authorities the Personal Information and any other information in its power or is accesible through its systems and is required in accordance with applicable legal and regulatory requirements as the case may warrant. 

**6\. Consent.**

In accepting these General Terms, the Users express their consent for their personal information to be incorporated in the Personal Information Catalogue and be given automated treatment by TODOENTRADAS, S.L. with the previously mentioned purposes.

Also, the User expresses acceptance and authorization so that TODOENTRADAS, S.L. may ceed the personal information, including international transfer of the private information to third parties indicated in Clause4. with the purposes there stated. 

**7\. Rights to access, cancel, rectify, and deny Users.**

TODOENTRADAS, S.L. guarantees Users the right to access, cancel, rectify, and deny in any case under the terms of effective legislation. For this reason, and in accordance with Organic Law 15/1999 on the Protection of Personal Information of Spain and its regulations, Users may make use of their rights by sending an express request and a copy of their official ID, through the following means: 

E-Mail: [support@ticketbis.net](mailto:contacto@ticketbis.com)

Fax: 915767599

Correo Postal: Conde de Aranda Street No 20, 4 derecha, 28001, Madrid, Spain.

In the same manner, the Users may cancel their subscription to any of the services facilitated by clicking in the subscription cancellation link included in all e-mails sent by TODOENTRADAS, S.L.
